Can't get the monkey off your back?
죽을 맛인가요?
그럼 마셔 버리세요!
'몽키샤인 맥주'!
Then put it in your mouth...
... with Monkeyshine Beer!
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
'몽키샤인 맥주'!
정글에서 벗어나세요!
Monkeyshine Beer.
Because it's a jungle out there!
That commercial always
makes me so sad.
저 광고만 보면 슬퍼져
그래도 남자가 맥주를 따면
여자가 달려들잖아
But then the guy opens his beer
and girls run at him...
그럼 됐지 뭐
...so everything works out okay.
저 원숭이를 보면
마르셀이 생각나거든
I meant because the monkey
reminds me of Marcel.
I can see that.
무슨 말인지 알겠어
커다란 갈색 눈과
새침한 턱이 똑같잖아
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
마르셀도 원숭이니까!
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
마르셀을 보낸 것이
잘한 것인지 모르겠어
I wonder if I did the right thing,
giving him away.
Ross, you had to. He was
humping everything in sight.
어쩔 수 없었잖아
발정기였으니까
내 바비 인형은 결혼해도
흰 드레스를 못 입을 거야
My Malibu Barbie will no longer
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
모자를 빌려 주면 거기다
쥐똥 같은 걸 담아 주곤 했지
...and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
그 땐 웃겼잖아, 내가 부장님
모자에 그랬다가 어땠게?
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss's hat....
싸가지 없다고
일장 훈시를 들었지
Suddenly, I had this big
"attitude problem."
The One With the Super Bowl, Part 1
이게 뭐게?
Hey, check it out!
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
음악 깔아 줘?
No. My first fan mail!
아냐, 첫 팬레터가 왔어!
"Dear Dr. Ramoray:
'라모레이 박사님께
당신을 너무나 사랑해요'
I love you and would do
anything to have you."
My gosh! "Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford."
'당신의 열렬한 팬
에리카 포드'
Oh, wait.
잠깐만
"P.S. Enclosed, please find
14 of my eyelashes."
'추신, 제 눈썹 14가닥을
함께 넣었어요'
이런 험한 세상에서는
이게 결혼을 뜻할 수도 있어
In Crazy World, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days Of Our
Lives. This came to your apartment.
방송국이 아니라
너희 아파트로 왔잖아
우표도 없는 걸 보면
직접 왔다는 거야
She was in our building.
Oh, my God.
맙소사!
I got my very own stalker!
내게도 스토커가 생겼어!
- 안녕
- 어서 와
Where are you off to?
어디 가는데 빼 입었어?
There's a paleontology
conference in L.A.
LA에서 고생물학자
세미나가 있거든
So I figured I'd go and drive down
to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
기왕 간 김에 동물원의
마르셀도 만나 보려고
자기가 원숭이란 걸 알면
녀석도 놀랄 거야
He will be surprised.
Till he realizes he's a monkey...
사람이 아니라고 하면
펄쩍 뛸걸
...and isn't capable of that emotion.
피비, 그 멋쟁이가 왔어
Phoebe? That really cute guy
is here again.
Okay, so everyone...
내가 너희들에게 웃긴
얘기를 하는 척해
... pretend I'm telling you a story
and it's really funny.
무조건 웃으라고
지금이야!
So everyone just laugh. Now!
I know, I know!
맞아, 그렇다니까!
- 안녕하세요
- 네
I'm Rob Donan.
전 롭 도난입니다
Hi, Rob Donan.
- 안녕하세요, 롭 도난 씨
- 음악엔 문외한이지만
I don't know anything about music,
but I think you're really great.
당신의 노래를 듣고
정말 좋았어요
와!
Anyway, I schedule performers
for children's libraries.
제가 어린이 도서관에서
공연을 준비하는데
And I was thinking, have you thought
about playing your songs for kids?
아이들을 위해서
노래 부를 생각 있어요?
I would love to have kids...
나도 아이 갖고 싶어요!
아니, 애들이 제 노래를
들었으면 좋겠다고요
...hear me play the songs
that I will write for them.
What do we do for dinner?
- 저녁 어떻게 할까?
- 집에서 밥이나 해먹지 뭐
We could cook for ourselves.
- 누구세요?
- 에리카예요
It's Erika.
My God. The stalker!
- 스토커야!
- 열려 있네요, 들어갈게요
Never mind. It's open.
Hitting her with a frying pan
is a good idea.
프라이팬으로 때리는 것도
좋은 생각이지만
만약의 사태를 위한
대비책도 있어야지!
But we want a backup plan,
just in case she isn't a cartoon!
Let's get out of here!
도망가자!
The one time they're not home!
- 필요할 땐 꼭 없더라!
- 좋아!
We'll leave.
When we pass her...
나가자, 만난 적 없으니
날 못 알아볼 거야
...she won't know me,
because we never met!
그건 라디오 출연자나
쓰는 방법이잖아!
That's how radio stars
escape stalkers!
She's coming!
온다!
It's me.
저예요
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
이렇게 죽게 될 줄이야
You ready?
- 준비됐어?
- 잠깐만!
Wait, wait, wait!
- 안녕하세요
- 에리카!
Erika!
-Mr. Geller?
-Yes, hi.
- 겔러 씨?
- 네, 안녕하세요
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
동물원 책임자 딘 립손인데
궁금한 게 있으시다고요?
You had a question?
제가 작년에 기증한
원숭이가 없어서요
I can't find the monkey I donated
last year. He's a capuchin...
마르셀이란 이름에
반응하는 원숭이였는데
...answers to the name Marcel?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
안 좋은 소식을 전해
유감이군요
Marcel has passed on.
마르셀은 죽었습니다
Oh, my God. What happened?
맙소사... 어떻게요?
아주 아팠거든요
He got sick,
and then he got sicker...
상태가 계속 악화되더니
좀 나아지더라구요
...and then he got a little better.
But then he died.
그러다 죽었죠
I can't believe this!
말도 안 돼요!
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller.
But you know, there's an old saying:
죄송합니다, 겔러 씨
이런 속담도 있잖아요
"Sometimes monkeys die."
'때론 원숭이도 죽는다'
좋은 속담은 아니지만
It's not a great saying...
... but it certainly is fitting today.
이 상황에 딱 들어맞죠
-Someone should've called me.
-I'm sorry.
- 연락을 해줬어야죠
- 죄송합니다
Look, I know this can't
bring him back...
마르셀은 죽었지만
성의의 표시입니다
... but here, it's just a gesture.
Zoo dollars?
동물원 돈이요?
Yes, and come see the bird show
at 4. The macaws wear hats.
네, 4시에 새 공연 보세요
앵무새가 모자를 쓰거든요
It's a lot cuter
if your monkey hasn't just died.
마르셀이 안 죽었다면
더 귀여웠을 텐데요
I know.
알아
I can't believe Joey's having
lunch with his stalker!
조이가 스토커랑
점심을 먹는단 말야?
어떤 여자야?
What is she like?
You remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
'미저리'에 나온
케시 베이츠 알지?
그 여자하고 정 반대로 생겼어
Well, she looks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
- 미친 여자 아냐?
- 아니, 완전히 돌았어
Oh, no, no.
She's a total whack-job.
조이가 정말 라모레이
박사인 줄 안다니까
She thinks that Joey is
actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
And he's going out with her?
그런 여자랑 사귄다고?
말려야 돼
He cannot pursue this.
TV 속의 인물을 사랑하면
사랑도 못하니?
Just because this woman sees Joey
through the magical box...
...in her living room
doesn't mean she's not a person.
그런 사람도 사람인데
그 여자도 행복해지고
사랑할 권리가 있다고
Does she not deserve happiness?
Does she not deserve love?
Why are you looking at me? He's
the one who wants to boff the maniac!
왜 날 쳐다봐?
사이코 만나는 건 조이라고!
- 괜찮아요?
- 네, 좀 긴장돼서요
Are you okay?
No. I'm just nervous.
Maybe if I just picture them all
in their underwear....
쟤들이 벗고 있다고 상상하면
좀 낫겠죠
좋은 생각이 아니에요
전 남자가수도 그러다 잘렸죠
That's not a good idea. That's
the reason the last guy got fired.
I'm used to playing for grownups.
전 어른들 앞에서만
불렀거든요
Grownups drink their coffee
and do their grownup thing.
어른들은 커피 마시면서
딴짓들을 하잖아요
한데 아이들은...
집중해서 듣잖아요
And kids...
...Iisten.
It's just a huge responsibility.
책임감도 무겁고...
What?
왜요?
Are you gonna kiss me?
나한테 키스하려고요?
I was thinking about it.
그럴까 생각했죠
좋아요
이제 됐어요
얘들아, 노래하자!
Alrighty! Let's play some tunes!
-Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
-Hi, Phoebe!
- 안녕, 난 피비야
- 안녕하세요
좋아
I'm gonna play some songs
about grandparents, okay?
할머니, 할아버지에 대한
노래를 불러 줄게, 알았지?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
세상 사람들은
할머니를 아주 좋아하죠
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
기차와 자전거도 사 주세요
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
요며칠 저녁을 안 드시더니
살이 점점 빠지셨어요
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
너희 부모님은 할머니가
페루에 가셨다고 하시지만
Now your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
사실은 돌아가신 거란다
너희도 결국엔 죽겠지
- 드레이크, 정말 굉장하죠?
- 그래요
-Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it is.
What?
뭐가요?
Well, here we sit, devil-may-care...
이렇게 함께 있는 게요
...and a while ago you were
reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
좀 전까지 시몬의 척추를
접합하고 있었잖아요
That was a tricky one.
아주 힘들었죠
실제론 10시간 이상
걸리는 대수술이지만
In reality...
...that operation takes 10 hours.
But they only showed it for 2 minutes.
그들은 2분 만에 끝냈죠
Who's "they"?
그들이라뇨?
No one.
아니에요
당신은 재능이 뛰어나요
Drake, you are so talented.
Let me see those hands.
손 좀 보여 줘요
Oh, these hands,
these beautiful hands.
손이 너무 예뻐요
먹어 버리고 싶어요
I could just eat them.
But I won't.
하지만 참죠
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
안 그럼 제 시계가
떨어지겠죠
No, seriously.
정말로요
These hands...
이 손은 사람을 살리는
마법의 손이에요
...these miracle, magical,
life-giving hands.
만지고만 있어도 좋아요
하나만 빨아도 될까요?
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even lick one?
All right. Just one.
좋아요, 딱 하나만
You're good at that.
아주 잘하네요
목에 뭐가 걸렸어요!
Oh, my God! Someone!
He's choking!
Is anyone here a doctor?
손님 중에 의사 계세요?
그럼요!
명의가 여기 계세요!
Yes, the best doctor in Salem!
드레이크 라모레이 박사님!
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
Meet me in the nocturnal
house in 15 minutes.
야행성 동물관에서
15분 후에 만납시다
Hey, look. I don't really enjoy
being with other men that way.
전 남자랑 그렇게
만나는 것 싫어해요
But, zoo dollars?
동물원 돈 줄까요?
It's about your monkey!
당신 원숭이 문제요
It's alive.
아직 살아 있소
왜 저 남자를 돕지 않았죠?
I don't understand.
Why didn't you help that man?
전 신경외과의인데
아까 그 경우는...
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
...and that was clearly a case of...
음식물 질식이었잖아요
... "foodal chokage."
- 솔직히 말할게요
- 아니에요
I gotta tell you something
아무 말도 말아요
You don't have to tell me anything.
내게 사소한 것까지
설명하실 필요 없어요
You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
제가 뭐라고 라모레이
박사님을 의심하겠어요?
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Drake Ramoray?
I should be happy to be near you.
박사님 곁에 있어서
너무나 행복해요!
어이...
Hey, l
어이 뭐요?
Hey what?
그냥 '어이'였어요
That's it. Just hey!
블루스 추면 좋아서
'어이! ' 그러잖아요
Like at the end of a dance. Hey!
There'll be times when you get older
늙으면 딴사람이랑
자고 싶어질 거야
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
너희를 좋아하게 말야
하지만 절대 그러지 마
'Cause...
왜냐하면...
... that's another thing...
그러면 안 좋거든
모두 복창!
... that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
그러면 안 좋거든
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
- 멋졌어!
- 무형식의 아름다움!
-Excellent!
-Very informative!
적절하지 않은 가사!
Not at all inappropriate!
모두 들어 줘서 고마워
뒤쪽에 쿠키가 있어
Thank you for coming, everybody!
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
아주 좋았어요
The kids loved you.
아이들이 당신을 좋아해요
Yea! I rock!
그럼요, 난 최고거든요
아이들에게 진실을
알려 줬잖아요
And you know why?
Because you told the truth.
Nobody ever tells kids the truth.
진실을 말하는 어른은
드물거든요
You were incredible!
정말 대단했어요!
그런데요?
But...?
-How'd you know there was a "but"?
-I sense these things.
- 또 할말 있는 거 알았어요?
- 본능이죠
It was either "but" or "butter."
아님 말을 안 꺼냈겠죠
부모님들의 요청인데
The thing is, I think
some of the parents...
...they were hoping that...
다음엔 가축에 대한 노래를
불러 줬으면 해요
...you'd play more songs
about barnyard animals.
I can do that.
그럴게요
Really?
- 정말로요?
- 그럼요
Because that would be fantastic!
그럼 더할 나위가 없죠
What? You wanna kiss me?
왜요?
나랑 키스하고 싶어요?
I'm thinking about it.
생각 중이에요
The bat.
박쥐! 암흑의 대사!
Ambassador of darkness.
Flitting out of his cave
like a winged messenger.
날개 달린 메신저처럼
동굴을 뛰쳐나오죠
소름끼치는 장님 괴물!
Sightless specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
내 원숭이는요?
Oh, yeah, right.
참, 그렇지
There was a break-in...
몇 달 전에 도둑이
침입해서는
...a few months back.
Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
당신 원숭이를 훔쳐갔어요
The zoo told me
that my monkey was dead!
동물원 측에서는
죽었다고 하던데
The zoo!
동물원!
You believe everything
the zoo tells you?
동물원의 말이라면
무조건 다 믿어요?
That's the only thing
the zoo's ever told me.
동물원으로부터 들은 건
그 얘기뿐인데
당연히 죽었다고 하겠죠
알려지면 귀찮으니까
Of course they'll say that!
They don't want the bad publicity.
It's all a great big cover-up.
진실을 은폐하려는 거죠
고위층이 이번 사건에
관련돼 있어요
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
립손이란 사람?
립손이 알아요?
Lipson knows?
Lipson knows, huh?
안단 말이지...
안녕, 포섬!
Hello, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
나무에 거꾸로 매달려
살아가는 수수께끼의...
-Taunting gravity
-Buddy, my monkey. My monkey?
내 원숭이요!
거리에서...
Word on the street
When I say "street," I mean those
pretend streets here at the zoo.
여기서 거리란 동물원의
가짜 거리를 말하죠
알아요
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career...
당신 원숭이가
새 일을 찾았어요
...in the entertainment field.
That's all I know.
일종의 희극단인데
난 거기까지만 알아요
This is unbelievable!
말도 안 돼!
So what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
이 정보의 가치가
얼마나 되죠?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
뇌물을 달라고요?
Maybe.
아마도
But you already told me everything.
벌써 다 말했잖아요
Check it out.
이걸 봐
He actually is
the Monkeyshine monkey!
마르셀이 몽키샤인의
그 원숭이라고
어떻게 할 거야?
What'll you do?
맥주 회사에 전화해서
찾아보려고
I'm gonna call the beer company
and try to find him.
짐마차 잃어버렸을 때
나도 그랬었지
That's what I did
when I lost my Clydesdales.
Okay, hi again!
안녕, 얘들아
안녕하세요!
Hi, Phoebe!
오늘은 가축에 대한
노래를 부를 거야
Today, we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animals.
초원의 소는 '음메' 운다네
Oh, the cow in the meadow goes "moo"
Then the farmer hits him
And grinds him up
농부는 그 소를 갈아서
우리 햄버거를 만드네
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
이번엔 치킨!
Only you who can save her, Drake!
자네만이 살릴 수 있어!
전 의사지
신이 아닙니다!
Damn it! I'm a doctor.
I'm not God!
There goes my whole belief system.
의사들에 대한 믿음이
그냥 깨지네
에리카예요
It's Erika.
Quick! Shut off the TV.
맙소사!
빨리 TV 꺼!
I wanna see what happens!
어떻게 되는지는 봐야지!
I get Leslie out of the coma
then we make out.
내가 레슬리를 깨워내고
애무를 해
How can that be?
You were kissing Sabrina!
어떻게? 방금 사브라니와
키스하고 있었잖아?
Rachel, it's a world
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
조이가 신경외과의인
세상을 그린 드라마야
Hey, Erika. Come in.
에리카, 들어와요
How did you get here so fast?
I just saw you in Salem.
빨리도 왔네요
방금 살렘에서 봤는데
Right, they choppered me in.
헬기를 타고 돌아왔죠
무슨 일이에요?
What's up?
You're having a little party too!
파티를 하고 계셨군요
그 여자 여기 있어요?
-ls she here?
-Who?
누구요?
사브리나!
둘의 관계를 알아요
Sabrina. I know about you two!
I saw you today, kissing
in the doctor's lounge.
휴게실에서 키스하는 걸
내가 똑똑히 봤어요
- 그런 게 아니라...
- 나만 사랑한다고 해놓고!
It's not what you think
You told me I was the only one!
All right, look.
That's it.
좋아요
더는 못 참아요
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
이제 우리 그만 만나요
I should have told you
a long time ago...
진작 말했어야 했지만
난 라모레이 박사가 아니에요
... but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not even a doctor. I'm an actor.
I just pretend to be a doctor.
의사도 아니고
의사인 척 연기하는 배우죠!
Oh, my God! Do the people
at the hospital know?
맙소사!
병원 사람들도 그걸 알아요?
누구 나 좀 도와 줄래?
Somebody wanna help me out here?
방법이 있어!
Oh, I know! I know!
Where am I?
여기가 어디죠?
University Hospital...
대학병원이요
당신이 지난 18년 간
지낸 곳이죠
... where you've been
for the last 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
당신은 여기 있는데
어떻게 TV에 나오죠?
Because it's a TV show!
저건 드라마예요
What are you getting at?
드레이크
무슨 말을 하려는 거죠?
난 드레이크가 아녜요!
I'm not Drake!
맞아요
드레이크가 아니에요
That's right!
He's not Drake. He's...
저 친구는 드레이크의
쌍둥이 동생인 한스예요!
... Hans Ramoray, Drake's evil twin!
정말인가요?
Is this true?
Yes! Yes, it is true!
그래요, 사실이에요
제가 잘 알죠
And I know this...
드레이크인 척하면서
내게 접근했었거든요
... because he pretended
to be Drake to sleep with me!
And then he told me
he would run away with me!
나랑 도망간다고 했는데
새빨간 거짓말!
And he didn't!
And you left the toilet seat up,
you bastard!
화장실 변기 안 내렸지
이 나쁜 자식아!
Is all this true?
모두 사실인가요?
그래요
유감이지만 사실이에요
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
당신은 좋은 사람을
만나야 해요, 에리카
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the real Drake.
He's the one you fell in love with.
당신이 사랑하는
드레이크를 찾아가요
Go to Salem. Find him!
살렘으로 가서 그를 찾아요!
He's the guy for you!
당신이 사랑하는 남자를!
Oh, Hans!
한스...
Hans?
한스? 한스!
Hans!
Yo, evil twin!
못된 쌍둥이 형제!
그렇지!
안녕, 에리카
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good luck in Salem.
살렘에서 그를 찾아요
Take care.
잘 가요
I'll never forget you, Hans.
당신을 못 잊을 거예요
물 끼얹은 사람 다 나와!
All right.
The people who threw the water!
돕느라고 그랬잖아
Helping you out!
Fired?
해고요? 왜요?
Why?
The library board got a lot
of complaints from parents...
부모님들이 도서관의
위원회 측에
노래가사에 대해서
불만을 터뜨렸거든요
...about the stuff in your songs.
I can't believe it!
말도 안 돼요!
아이들은 진실을 원한다고
위원회에 설명했어요?
Did you tell your board that
the kids want to hear the truth?
아뇨
알았어요
I see.
평범한 동요를 부르면요?
Maybe if you just played
some regular kiddy songs?
싫어요!
나더러 보라색 공룡 같은
광대가 되라고요?
What do you want me to be?
Like some...
...stupid, big,
like, purple dinosaur?
- 바니가 되란 소리가 아녜요
- 바니가 누군데요?
You don't have to be Barney.
Who's Barney?
마르셀을 찾았는데 건강하고
여기 뉴욕에서 영화를 찍는대!
I tracked down Marcel and get this.
He's healthy, he's happy...
...and he's in New York filming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
'아웃브레이크 II
바이러스의 맨해튼 침공! '
정말?
You're kidding!
- 내 어이가 없어서
- 누가 아니래
-This is amazing!
-I know.
난 TV의 단역인데
원숭이는 영화를 찍어?
I finally get a part on TV,
and the monkey's making movies.
레이첼, 나 준비됐어
Rachel, I'm ready.
진실을 말하는 가수가
여기 있나요?
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing lady is, who tells the truth?
난데 왜?
I guess that's me.
찾았다!
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
여자와 남자를 동시에
사랑하는 남자가 있어
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
이를 양성애라고 하는데
사람들은 믿지를 않아
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
너무 흥분돼
1년 만에 보는 거잖아
This is exciting! I haven't
seen my monkey in a year.
What, you never
look down in the shower?
샤워하면서 안 봤어?
다들 원숭이를 성기에
비교하는데 뭘 그래?
I'm not allowed to make one joke
in the "monkey is penis" genre?
좀 물러서 주세요
어서요!
Back up, please.
Back up. Come on.
말씀 좀 물을게요
원숭이는 어디서 만나죠?
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
I'm sorry.
It's a closed set.
미안하지만
비공개 촬영이라서
모르시겠지만
전 그 원숭이 친구예요
I'm sorry, you don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
예전에 함께 살았죠
We used to live together.
내게는 수평타가 달린
초대형 보트가 있지
And I have a time share
in the Poconos with Flipper.
There he is!
저기 있어!
Hey! Buddy!
이봐, 친구!
마르셀!
Marcel! Marcel!
In the jungle
장엄한 정글에
사자가 잠들어 있네
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
장엄한 정글에
사자가 잠들어 있네
The lion sleeps tonight
They won't take you to the vet
수의사에게 안 데려갈게
수의사도 널 싫어하니까
You're obviously not
Their favorite pet
냄새나는 고양이
사실 네 잘못은 아냐
Smelly cat
It's not your fault
- 왜요?
- 미안해요
-What?
-I'm sorry.
뭐 잘못됐어요?
What's wrong with that?
You might want to pick
a more masculine note.
좀 남자답게 소리를 내봐요